{
    "quizId" : "111111",
    "quizTitle" : "MyQuiz",
    "quizDomain" :  {
        "domainId":120,
        "domain" : "MySQL"
},
    "quizDuration" : "1",
    "questions" : [
        {
            "questionId" : "811",
            "question" : "Row is synonymous with the term",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "record",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "record",
            "option2" : "relation",
            "option3" : "column",
            "option4" : "field"
        },
        
        {
            "questionId" : "812",
            "question" : "SQL stands for",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Structured Query Language",
               "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Sequential Query Language",
            "option2" : "Structural Query Language",
            "option3" : "Sequential Question Language",
            "option4" : "Structured Query Language"
        },
        
       {
            "questionId" : "813",
            "question" : "A relation is considered a",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Column",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Column",
            "option2" : "one-dimensional table",
            "option3" : "two-dimensional table",
            "option4" : "three-dimensional table"
        },
    
      {
            "questionId" : "814",
            "question" : "A key",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "identifies a row",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "must always be composed of two or more columns",
            "option2" : "can only be one column",
            "option3" : "identifies a row",
            "option4" : "identifies a column"
        },

       {
            "questionId" : "815",
            "question" : "The primary key is selected from the?",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "candidate keys",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "determinants",
            "option2" : "candidate keys",
            "option3" : "composite keys",
            "option4" : "foreign keys"
        },
       
        {
            "questionId" : "816",
            "question" : "In the relational model, relationships between relations or tables are created by using?",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "foreign keys",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "determinants.",
            "option2" : "candidate keys",
            "option3" : "composite keys",
            "option4" : "foreign keys"
        },
        
        {
            "questionId" : "817",
            "question" : "A tuple is a(n)",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "row of a table",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "two dimensional table",
            "option2" : "column of a table",
            "option3" : "row of a table",
            "option4" : "key of a table"
        },

       {
            "questionId" : "818",
            "question" : "A relation in this form is free of all modification anomalies",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Domain/key normal form",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "First normal form",
            "option2" : "Second normal form",
            "option3" : "Third normal form",
            "option4" : "Domain/key normal form"
        },
         
     
         
       {
            "questionId" : "820",
            "question" : " The  ________  clause is used to list the attributes desired in the result of a query",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "select",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "where",
            "option2" : "select",
            "option3" : "from",
            "option4" : "Distinct"
        },

        {
            "questionId" : "821",
            "question" : " SELECT * FROM employee WHERE salary>10000 AND dept_id=101;",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "All the field of employee relation",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Salary, dept_id",
            "option2" : " Employee",
            "option3" : "Salary",
            "option4" : "All the field of employee relation"
        },

   
        
        
       {
            "questionId" : "823",
            "question" : "SELECT * FROM employee WHERE dept_name='Comp Sci'; In the SQL given above there is an error. Identify the error",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : " “Comp Sci”",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : " Dept_name ",
            "option2" : "Employee",
            "option3" : " “Comp Sci”",
            "option4" : "From"
        },

   

       {
           
            "questionId" : "825",
            "question" : "  _____ operator is used for appending two strings",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "||",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "&",
            "option2" : " %",
            "option3" : "||",
            "option4" : "_"
        },
  
       {

           "questionId" : "826",
            "question" : "A _________ consists of a sequence of query and/or update statements",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Transaction",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Transaction",
            "option2" : "Commit",
            "option3" : "Rollback",
            "option4" : "Flasback"
        },

        {
           "questionId" : "827",
            "question" : "Which of the following makes the transaction permanent in the database?",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "commit",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "view",
            "option2" : "commit",
            "option3" : "rollback",
            "option4" : "flasback"
        },
        
  
          {
           "questionId" : "829",
            "question" : "______ will undo all statements up to commit ",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Rollback",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Transaction",
            "option2" : "Flashback",
            "option3" : "Rollback",
            "option4" : "Abort"
        },
     
       
          {
           "questionId" : "830",
            "question" : "A stored procedure in SQL is a___________",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Group of Transact-SQL statements compiled into a single execution plan",
              "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Group of Transact-SQL statements compiled into a single execution plan",
            "option2" : "Block of functions",
            "option3" : "Group of distinct SQL statements ",
            "option4" : "None of the mentioned"
        },

         {
           "questionId" : "831",
            "question" : "How many types of stored procedure are present in SQL server?",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "4",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "3",
            "option2" : "4",
            "option3" : "8",
            "option4" : "5"
        },
       
  
         
       {
           "questionId" : "833",
            "question" : " The number of attributes in relation is called as its",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Degree",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Cardinality",
            "option2" : "Degree",
            "option3" : "Tuples ",
            "option4" : " Entity"
        },
        
        {
           "questionId" : "834",
            "question" : " _________ joins are SQL server default",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Inner",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Outer",
            "option2" : "Inner",
            "option3" : "Equi ",
            "option4" : " None of the mentioned"
        },
        
        {
           "questionId" : "835",
            "question" : " The _____________ is essentially used to search for patterns in target string",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Like Predicate",
             "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Like Predicate",
            "option2" : "Null Predicate",
            "option3" : "In Predicate ",
            "option4" : "Out Predicate"
        },
       
        {
           "questionId" : "836",
            "question" : " Which of the join operations do not preserve non matched tuples",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Inner join",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Left outer join",
            "option2" : "Right outer join",
            "option3" : "Inner join",
            "option4" : "Natural join"
        },
        
          
    
        
         {
           "questionId" : "838",
            "question" : "Which of the following invokes functions in sql",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "Callable statements",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "Prepared Statements",
            "option2" : "Connection statement",
            "option3" : "Callable statements",
            "option4" : "All of the mentioned"
        },
        
        
       {
           "questionId" : "840",
            "question" : "Nesting limit pf stored procedure is upto ___level?",
            "difficulty" : "EASY",
            "correctOption" : "32",
            "domain" : {
                           "domainId":120,
                           "domain" : "MySQL"
            },
            "option1" : "30",
            "option2" : "34",
            "option3" : "32",
            "option4" : "36"
        }
    ]
}        

